A Guide to the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation records FA248
Rockefeller Archive Center
Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation records
1956-2005, bulk 1978-1999
bulk
Rockefeller Archive Center
Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation
Southern Bancorp
FA248
1 Cubic Feet 141 reels
Biographical/Historical note
Winthrop Rockefeller Biography
Winthrop Rockefeller was born May 1, 1912, the fourth son of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller. Affectionately known as "Win" to family and friends, he attended the Lincoln School, a progressive co-educational preparatory school connected with Teachers College of Columbia University in New York City, and the Loomis School in Windsor, Connecticut before entering Yale University in 1931. He left school in 1934 and worked in the Texas oil fields as a roughneck and roustabout for the Humble Oil and Refining Company.
Rockefeller returned to New York City by 1937, but after a series of executive positions he enlisted in the Army as a private in January 1941. During World War II he participated in the assault landings on Guam, Leyte, and Okinawa in the Pacific. Aboard the troop transport Henrico, en route to Okinawa, he was wounded in a kamikaze attack. Among his decorations were the Bronze Star with Oak Leaf Cluster and the Purple Heart. He attained the rank of lieutenant colonel by the time of his discharge in 1946.
After the war Rockefeller returned to the Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, but resigned in 1951. By 1953 he decided that he needed a change of scenery from New York and settled permanently in Arkansas. That June he purchased a 927-acre tract atop Petit Jean Mountain, 60 miles west of Little Rock, where he built Winrock Farms into an internationally recognized cattle operation whose pure-bred Santa Gertrudis cattle drew buyers from many parts of the world. The "WR" brand became internationally known as a symbol of excellence among Santa Gertrudis owners.
In 1955 Governor Orval Faubus appointed Rockefeller to the new Arkansas Industrial Development Commission, where he served eight years as chairman. Under his leadership, the commission helped 600 industries locate to or expand in Arkansas, creating more than 100,000 job opportunities.
As the state Republican National committeeman beginning in 1961, he led efforts to bring about a two-party system in heavily Democratic Arkansas. He ran for governor in 1964 and received 44% of the vote, which doubled the previous record of total votes cast in the state for any Republican candidate. "We sincerely believe we won a victory, even in defeat," he said. He won the election for governor in 1966 and took office in 1967, becoming the first Republican governor in Arkansas in 94 years. He won re-election in 1968 but lost in a three-way race in 1970. His two terms in office were marked by a state legislature that was overwhelmingly Democratic. At one time, there were 97 Democrats and three Republicans in the Arkansas House of Representatives.
He considered one of his greatest challenges as governor to be the reform of the state penal system. He brought in professional penologists as part of his corrective measures. His administration also shut down open gambling in Hot Springs, a resort area. Other reform legislation enacted under his administration included governmental reorganization and tighter insurance and securities regulations. He was especially proud of the enactment of the Freedom of Information Act of 1967, which had the effect of opening official meetings to the public. "We have taken the government out of the smoke-filled rooms and returned it to the people," he said.
Although viewed by some as the "black sheep" of his generation of Rockefellers, Winthrop Rockefeller contributed money and time to a number of philanthropic projects and causes that the family favored. His attitude toward wealth and its uses echoed the sentiments of his father: "I have enjoyed the personal use of money," he wrote in his unpublished "A Letter to My Son." "But I have gotten the greatest satisfaction from using it to advance my beliefs in human relations - human values.... The biggest returns from the investment of money come in what we can call philanthropic achievements, in the encouragement of people who make our business grow, making jobs and security for others, and in the development of men, their happiness, their usefulness and their freedom." He was chairman of the board of Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, which his father established, and in 1940 was one of the founders the Rockefeller Brothers Fund, of which he was a trustee. He also served as a trustee of the National Urban League, 1940-1964.
He undertook several philanthropic projects to promote the development of education and public health in Arkansas, creating the Rockwin Fund (renamed the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation in 1974) in 1956 to fund such projects. He was instrumental in establishing the Arkansas Arts Center, a facility designed to serve the entire state from its central location in Little Rock. He was a trustee of several schools, including Vanderbilt University, and was a member of the Southern Advisory Board for the Institute of International Education. He established student aid funds at several Arkansas colleges and in 1956 started the Arkansas Opportunity Fund to provide scholarships to qualifying students. He served in an advisory capacity during the development of both the University of Arkansas Medical Center and the Graduate Institute of Technology in Little Rock. In recognition of this and other services, he received several honorary degrees, including ones from the University of Arkansas, Hendrix College, New York University, the College of William and Mary, College of the Ozarks and Southwestern at Memphis.
Winthrop Rockefeller was married twice. He married the former Barbara Sears on February 14, 1948. They had one son before divorcing in 1954. On June 11, 1956 he married Jeannette Edris. She had a son and daughter from a previous marriage. The couple divorced in 1971. His son, Winthrop Paul Rockefeller, followed his father into Arkansas politics. He was elected the lieutenant governor of Arkansas in 1996 in a special election and was reelected to full four-year terms in 1998 and 2002.
On February 22, 1973, Winthrop Rockefeller died of cancer in Palm Springs, California. He was 60 years of age.
Biographical/Historical note
Institutional History
The Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation (WRF) began originally as the Rockwin Fund in 1957. It was a philanthropic foundation that was started by Winthrop Rockefeller to help the people of Arkansas, primarily through educational grants. When Governor Rockefeller passed away in 1973 Rockwin Fund became one of the two primary beneficiaries of the late Winthrop Rockefeller estate. With the large endowment bestowed on the organization, they changed their name and redefined their mission and vision and became the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation in 1974. Since Rockwin Fund focused primarily on education, by changing the scope of the grants the foundation was able to incorporate more of the late Governor's philanthropic passions, which was a larger scope of the welfare of the people of Arkansas.
The areas of interests now include: education, economic development and economic, social and racial justice in the state of Arkansas and only in Arkansas. Grants are only granted to organizations that are primarily based in Arkansas and will benefit the citizens of Arkansas over any other population.
The mission of the WRF is to improve the quality of life for the people of Arkansas and to promote systematic change.
Biographical/Historical note
Southern Development Bancorporation
In 1986, then Governor Bill Clinton and the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation announced an initiative to end decades of economic decline in rural Arkansas by creating new trends of investment in people, jobs, business and property. Southern Bancorp, a community development bank holding company, and its family of nonprofit development affiliates would emerge from that initiative. A consortium of private foundations, governmental entities, corporations and concerned individuals would come together later that year to incorporate Southern Bancorp.
Arrangement
The collection is divided into three series: Series 1 Administration Files, 1956-2005, Series 2 Grants, 1972-2001, Series 3 Financial, 1974-2000.
Each grant folder is divided into sections as applicable: original proposal, grant agreement or professional services agreement, then grant actions (divided by multiple years). The grants are organized by alphabetically by organization name and then by the grant number.
Reel and frame numbers represent the frame number where a particular folder title begins.
Scope and Contents note
The records of the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation span the years 1956 to 2005, with the majority of the records from the late 1970s to the late 1990s. During this time, the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation was making grants to organizations that were based in Arkansas and only did business in Arkansas.
Materials that have been separated and not filmed are noted throughout the collection with separation sheets and are available for viewing upon request, which includes photographs, previously published material and a videotape.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IV
Related Archival Materials note
Related Collections at the Rockefeller Archive Center: Winthrop Rockefeller Papers.
Existence and Location of Copies
A Note about the Microfilm: The Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation collection exists on 141 reels of 35mm preservation standard microfilm. Material that has been retained in its original format has been separated from the collection and is open for research. The microfilm collection will note the existence of original documentation with a separation sheet.
Microfiche Cards: There is an additional listing of microfiche cards that may be duplicates of the grants that have been filmed. An inventory is provided in this guide.
Conditions Governing Access
The archival material has been reformatted. Access to the original paper records is restricted. Microfilm user copies are available for research.
Charities -- Investments; Charities; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations; Charitable contributions; Arkansas; Economic development; Race and society; Education, Rural; Education; Social problems; Social policy; Social justice; Economics; Philanthropy; Education -- Arkansas; Social service; Social sciences; Southern Bancorp; Rockefeller, Winthrop
- Administrative Files, 1956-2005; 1 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
  - Rockwin Fund Incorporated, 1956-1983; 1 (Reel 1, Frame 2)
    Biographical/Historical note
    Winthrop Rockefeller founded this organization in 1956 when he moved to Little Rock, Arkansas. It was a philanthropic foundation that helped the people of Arkansas. Later it was redefined and became the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation.
    - Petition for the Incorporation of Rockwin Fund, Incorporated, 1956 (Reel 1, Frame 3)
    - Articles of Amendment of the Articles of Incorporation of the Rockwin Fund, Incorporated, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 11)
    - Rockwin Fund Review and Policy Statement, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 19)
    - Rockwin Program Study, Special Reports, 1967-1983 (Reel 1, Frame 200)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation, 1964-2005; 2 (Reel 1, Frame 427)
    Scope and Contents note
    This subseries covers the history of the organization with materials from the Board of Directors meetings and other governing committees, presidential files, and Winthrop Rockefeller.
    - Annual Reports, 1975-2004 (Reel 1, Frame 428)
    - Bylaws, Revised, 1989 September 9 (Reel 1, Frame 430)
    - Board of Directors (Reel 1, Frame 442)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1976 September 15 (Reel 1, Frame 443)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1976 December 13 (Reel 1, Frame 456)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1977 March 27-28 (Reel 1, Frame 466)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1977 July 18 (Reel 1, Frame 493)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1977 September 22 (Reel 1, Frame 500)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1977 December 9-10 (Reel 1, Frame 512)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1978 March 4 (Reel 1, Frame 589)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1978 May 27 (Reel 1, Frame 619)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1978 September 9 (Reel 1, Frame 637)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1978 December 15-17 (Reel 1, Frame 647)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1979 February 20 (Reel 1, Frame 703)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1979 March 2-3 (Reel 1, Frame 708)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1979 June 2 (Reel 1, Frame 718)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1979 September 8 (Reel 1, Frame 742)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1979 November 30-December 2 (Reel 1, Frame 757)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1980 March 8 (Reel 1, Frame 837)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1980 June 7 (Reel 1, Frame 865)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1980 September 6 (Reel 1, Frame 872)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1980 December 7 (Reel 1, Frame 881)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1981 March 7 (Reel 1, Frame 889)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1981 June 13 (Reel 1, Frame 895)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1981 September 11 (Reel 1, Frame 906)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1981 December 5 (Reel 1, Frame 923)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1982 February 26-27 (Reel 1, Frame 934)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1982 June 4-6 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1982 September 10-11 (Reel 2, Frame 214)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1982 December 3-4 (Reel 2, Frame 388)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1983 March 4-5 (Reel 2, Frame 488)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1983 June 3-5 (Reel 2, Frame 682)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1983 September 9-10 (Reel 2, Frame 819)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1983 December 2-3 (Reel 2, Frame 1018)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1984 March 2-3 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1984 June 1-3 (Reel 3, Frame 139)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1984 September 7-8 (Reel 3, Frame 308)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1984 November 30-December 1 (Reel 3, Frame 462)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1985 March 1-2 (Reel 3, Frame 606)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1985 May 31-June 2 (Reel 3, Frame 784)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1985 September 6-7 (Reel 3, Frame 1032)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1985 December 6-7 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1986 February 28-March 1 (Reel 4, Frame 210)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1986 May 30-June 1 (Reel 4, Frame 509)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1986 September 5-6 (Reel 4, Frame 808)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1986 December 5-6 (Reel 4, Frame 927)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1987 February 27-28 (Reel 4, Frame 1080)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1987 June 7 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1987 September 11-12 (Reel 5, Frame 182)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1987 December 5 (Reel 5, Frame 376)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1988 March 5 (Reel 5, Frame 485)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1988 June 3-5 (Reel 5, Frame 662)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1988 September 9-10 (Reel 5, Frame 803)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1988 December 2-3 (Reel 5, Frame 959)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1989 March 3-5 (Reel 5, Frame 1128)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1989 May 26-28 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1989 September 8-9 (Reel 6, Frame 198)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1989 November 30-December 1 (Reel 6, Frame 395)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1990 March 1-2 (Reel 6, Frame 577)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1990 May 30 1990 June 1-2 (Reel 6, Frame 728)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1990 September 6-8 (Reel 6, Frame 846)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1990 November 29-30 (Reel 6, Frame 1020)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1991 February 28-March 1 (Reel 6, Frame 1147)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1991 June 6-7 (Reel 6, Frame 1177)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1991 September 5-7 (Reel 7, Frame 1)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1991 December 12-13 (Reel 7, Frame 109)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1992 March 5-6 (Reel 7, Frame 347)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1992 June 4-5 (Reel 7, Frame 419)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1992 September 10-12 (Reel 7, Frame 601)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1992 December 11-12 (Reel 7, Frame 725)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1993 March 18-19 (Reel 7, Frame 928)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1993 June 3-4 (Reel 7, Frame 1028)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1993 September 9-11 (Reel 8, Frame 1)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1993 December 3-4 (Reel 8, Frame 107)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1994 March 3-5 (Reel 8, Frame 433)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1994 June 2-3 (Reel 8, Frame 506)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1994 September 8-10 (Reel 8, Frame 804)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1994 December 1-2 (Reel 8, Frame 935)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1995 March 2-4 (Reel 8, Frame 1221)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1995 June 1-2 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1995 September 6-9 (Reel 9, Frame 258)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1995 November 30-December 1 (Reel 9, Frame 396)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1996 February 28-29 1996 March 1 (Reel 9, Frame 580)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1996 June 6-7 (Reel 9, Frame 686)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1996 September 5-7 (Reel 9, Frame 914)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1996 December 7 (Reel 9, Frame 958)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1997 March 6-8 (Reel 9, Frame 1044)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1997 June 5-6 (Reel 9, Frame 1088)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1997 September 4-5 (Reel 9, Frame 1188)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1997 December 4-5 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1998 March 5-6 (Reel 10, Frame 138)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1998 June 5 (Reel 10, Frame 347)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1998 September 3-4 (Reel 10, Frame 473)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1999 March 4-5 (Reel 10, Frame 703)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1999 June 4 (Reel 10, Frame 958)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1999 September 17 (Reel 10, Frame 963)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 1999 December 3 (Reel 10, Frame 970)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2000 March 3-4 (Reel 10, Frame 976)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2000 June 2 (Reel 10, Frame 1088)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2000 September 7-8 (Reel 10, Frame 1094)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2000 December 7-8 (Reel 10, Frame 1100)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2001 March 2 (Reel 10, Frame 1108)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2001 June 1 (Reel 10, Frame 1114)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2001 September 7 (Reel 10, Frame 1118)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2001 December 7 (Reel 10, Frame 1122)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2002 March 8 (Reel 10, Frame 1126)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2002 June 7 (Reel 10, Frame 1131)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2002 September 6 (Reel 10, Frame 1138)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2002 December 6 (Reel 10, Frame 1144)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2003 March 7 (Reel 10, Frame 1149)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2003 June 6 (Reel 10, Frame 1154)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2003 September 5 (Reel 10, Frame 1159)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2003 December 5 (Reel 10, Frame 1165)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2004 March 3-5 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2004 June 3-4 (Reel 11, Frame 246)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2004 September 23-25 (Reel 11, Frame 770)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2004 December 2-3 (Reel 11, Frame 1051)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2005 March 4 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2005 June 3 (Reel 12, Frame 206)
      - Board of Directors, Retreat, 2005 September 8 (Reel 12, Frame 216)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2005 September 9 (Reel 12, Frame 251)
      - Board of Directors Meeting/Minutes, 2005 December 2 (Reel 12, Frame 412)
    - Other Committees (Reel 12, Frame 672)
      - Audit Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1995 August 25 (Reel 12, Frame 673)
      - Audit Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1996 May 8 (Reel 12, Frame 679)
      - Audit Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 2004 September 23 (Reel 12, Frame 683)
      - Audit Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 2005 March 3 (Reel 12, Frame 693)
      - Audit Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 2005 May 17 (Reel 12, Frame 753)
      - Audit Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 2005 August 31 (Reel 12, Frame 777)
      - Finance Committee, Historical, 1982-1984 (Reel 12A, Frame 1)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1978 January 1 (Reel 12A, Frame 30)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1979 November 1 (Reel 12A, Frame 54)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1980 November 7 (Reel 12A, Frame 71)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1981 November 6 (Reel 12A, Frame 83)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1982 January 14 (Reel 12A, Frame 87)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1982 October 29 (Reel 12A, Frame 109)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1983 October 13 (Reel 12A, Frame 125)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1985 December 6 (Reel 12A, Frame 131)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1986 December 5 (Reel 12A, Frame 141)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1987 December 4 (Reel 12A, Frame 209)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1988 December 2 (Reel 12A, Frame 236)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1989 November 30 (Reel 12A, Frame 250)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1990 November 29 (Reel 12A, Frame 267)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting, 1991 December 12 (Reel 12A, Frame 291)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting, 1992 December 11 (Reel 12A, Frame 328)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting, 1994 September 8 (Reel 12A, Frame 366)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting, 1995 September 6 (Reel 12A, Frame 395)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 1995 November 28 1995 November 30 (Reel 12A, Frame 423)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 2003 March 6 (Reel 12A, Frame 467)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 2003 June 5 (Reel 12A, Frame 517)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 2003 September 3 (Reel 12A, Frame 539)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting/Minutes, 2003 December 4 (Reel 12A, Frame 583)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting, 2005 February 25 (Reel 12A, Frame 606)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting, 2005 March 3 (Reel 12A, Frame 712)